https://www.dutchsweets.com/privacy.php

Cart ContentsCheckoutMy Account
Search
Home » Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.dutchsweets.com.
This web site agrees to notify you of:
What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site.
The organization collecting the information.
How the information is used.
With whom the information may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Dutch Sweets control.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection and Use
Dutch Sweets is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.
We will not now or ever, sell or rent this information to others. Dutch Sweets
collects information from our users at several different points
on our website.
Order
We request information from the user on our order form.
Here a user must provide contact information (like name and
shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number,
expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and
to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order,
this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the users hard drive containing
information about the cart. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to
any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance,
by setting a cookie on our site, we are able to track item selections.
If a user rejects the cookie, our site is not able to record item
selections in the cart, nor place an order. A user can browse the
site however.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's
movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
We will not share any information about our clients to anyone other than for
shipping or billing purposes.
We use UPS and the Postal Service to ship orders, and a credit card processing
company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain,
share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary
purposes.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users information.
When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information
is protected both online and off-line.
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive
information (such as credit card number and/or social security number),
that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption
software in the industry - SSL.
While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the
bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet
Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just
surfing..
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online,
we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line.
All of our users information, not just the sensitive information
mentioned above, is restricted in our offices.
Correction/Updating Personal Information:
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as
your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we
will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that
user's personal data provided to us.
Continue
Categories Licorice->Candy and ConfectionsSugar-FreeChocolate->CookiesCakes and BreadJams, Toppings & SpreadsDrinksClassic Dutch and German FoodIndonesian FoodBulkDelft and GiftsPennsylvania Dutch and Country
Manufacturers Please SelectAlbert HeijnAmish CountryAstraAtlantaAutodropAviateurAviateur or Mas..BahlsenBakkers WeeldeBanketfabriek S..BarkhuisBaronieBassettBechtleBolletjeBubsBurtonByler'sCalveCampinaCarlettiCasaliChoco SweetChristian StorzConfiserie Heid..ConimexCote d'OrDe BronDe HeerDe Molens Banke..De RuijterDouwe EgbertsDr. C. SoldanDr. OetkerDrosteDutch BakeryDutch CountryDutch GoldElysiaExtreme IceFaamFazerFelixFerreroFinnskaFortuinFriese VlagFrylingGerrit'sGeurtsGrabill Country..Gustaf'sGwoonHakHalvaHans FreitagHariboHellemaHeroHitschlerHonigHusker DuJahnkeJohn MoirKalfanyKatjaKatjesKindly'sKingKleneKnorrKonditorei Brud..KookaburraKoopmansKraepelien & Ho..KuhneLakrisalLangneseLaroshellLeafLekkerland Nede..LimeconLonkaLook-O-LookLotusLuMaggiMalacoMatthijsMeenkMerbaMilkaModdermanMrs. Miller'sNanningNapoleonNeerlandiaNipius BanketNuscoOldtimersPeynenburgPingvinPottersRaademakerRed BandRemiaRheila KonsulRiegeleinRijkenbergRitter SportScan-SweetSchluckwerderSicofSmith'sSteenlandThe Dutch Baker..TomsTrimexTrolliUnoxVan der BreggenVan DungenVan GilseVan MelleVan SlootenVan VlietVencoVerduynVerkadeVerstegenVerwijVillosaWickleinWieger Ketellap..WilhelminaZentis
What's New? Cremour Praline Cream Filled Chocolates$7.99
Shopping Cart 0 items
Bestsellers 100% Butter Stroopwafels- VerweijLakrisal Licorice RollDubbel Zoute Licorice by K&H (Gustaf's Double Salt Licorice)Echte Goude SpeculaasMunten Drop Licorice by K&H (Gustaf's Licorice Coins)De Ruijter Dark Chocolate Sprinkles (Hagelslag - Puur)SalmiakjesDe Ruijter Milk Chocolate Sprinkles (Hagelslag - Melk)Haring DropSchoolkrijt by Venco
Reviews Dutch Sweets reminds me of my youth. I consider myself a dub ..
